Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Incidents to be Reworked (APA Ethics Committee - Trial Letter (Box 34)
- Incidents and Others) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 1-50) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 51-100) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 101-150) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 151-199) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 200-250) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 251-300) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 301-350) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 351-400) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 401-450) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 451-500) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 501-550) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 551-600) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 601-650) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 651-700) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 701-750) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 751-800) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 801,-850) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 851-900) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 901-950) (Box 34)
- Original Incidents (File: 951-1000) (Box 34)
- Drafts
- Code for Keysort Cards
- Extra copies of Ethics Committee Materials
- David - Classified Psychology (Box 34)
- Sub-Committee on Sale and Distribution of Tests (Box 34, Folder 10.08)
- ."Developing a Code of Ethics--A First Report of Progress" (Box 34, Folder 11.05)
- Professional Ethics in Psychology (Box 34, Folder 11.14)
- (Black notebook) - Correspondence (Box 35)
- Manuscript: Notes for Talk on Ethics for Psychologists (Tulane (Box 35)
- University - December 16, 1950; The Louisiana Psychological Association) (Box 35)
- Ethics Symposium - Public Responsibility (Box 35)
- Reports of Group Discussions on Issues in Psychology
- Ethics - Manuscript: Ethical Standards in Research (Box 35)
- Ethics - Manuscript: Ethical Standards in Clinical and (Box 35)
- Counseling Consulting Relationships
- Ethics - Manuscript: "The Ethics of Counseling" (1951); C. (Box 35)
- Gilbert Wrenn's Presidential Address (Box 35)
- Ethics - Revision Materials and Letters (Box 35)
- Ethics -Manuscripts: Publications, Research, Professional (Box 35)
- Relationships
- Ethics - Outline for Handbook (Box 35)
- Ethics - Minutes of Meeting (January 26, 1951) (Box 35)
- Subcommittee - Public Responsibility (Box 35)
- Ethics - Publications Problems (Box 35)
- Ethics Meeting - June 3-4, 1951 (General Planning) (Box 35)
- Ethics Material - Public Responsibility (Box 35)
- Ethics Materials - State Psychological Associations (Box 35)
- Manuscript - Ethics and Public Responsibility (carbon copies of draft) (Box 35)
- Ethics - Manuscripts: Ethical Standards in Writing and Publishing (Box 35)
- Ethics - Manuscript: Ethical Standards in Teaching (Box 35)
- Ethics - Manuscript: Ethical Standards and Public Responsibility (Box 35)
- Ethics Symposium - Professional Relationships (Box 35)
- Ethics Subcommittees
- Ethics Committee
- Ethics Committee - Bills (1952) (Box 35)
- Ethics - A Report from the Committee on Ethical Standards for Psychology (Box 35)
- Ethics - Manuscript: Introduction (Sections 2,4 and 5) (Box 35)
- Ethics Committee Meeting (June, 1952) (Box 35)
- Ethics - Manuscript: Ethical Standards in Professional Relationships (Box 35)
- Commonwealth of Kentucky Department of Mental Health Annual Report (1954-1955) (Box 35)
- Materials from Psychology 486: "Mental Hygiene for Teachers" (Summer, 1951) (Box 35)
- Ethics - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
- Ethics for Students
- Education 555A - Cantrell, Anne (Box 35)
- 555A Human Development and Guidance (Box 35, Folder 2.21)
- Education 555A - Elfrink, Richard Joseph (Box 35)
- Desk 3: Program Planning (Box 35)
- Desk 5: Registration Materials (Box 35)
- Bibliography: Miscellaneous (Box 35)
- (2) boxes of index cards with multiple choice questions dealing with Psychology (Box 36)
- (1) box of cards with names of Chairmen of Psychology Department Notecards (Box 36)
- A - General Correspondence (Box 37)
- B-l General Correspondence: Ba (Box 37)
- B-2 General Correspondence: Be-Bq (Box 37)
- B-3 General Correspondence: Br (Box 37)
- C-l General Correspondence (Box 37)
- C-2 General Correspondence (Box 37)
- D Manuscript - Elizabeth Drews (Box 37)
- NAMH Correspondence: Special Reports (Box 37, Folder 13.51B)
- NAMH Correspondence: Special Reports (Box 37, Folder 13.51C)
- NAMH Correspondence: Special Reports (Box 37, Folder 13.51D)
- NAMH Correspondence: Special Reports (Box 37, Folder 13.51E)
- NAMH Correspondence: Special Reports (Box 37, Folder 13.51F)
- NAMHC Meeting, Washington (3/16-18/70) (Box 37, Folder 13.52)
- NAMHC Meeting, Washington (9/29-30/70) (Box 37, Folder 13.52)
- NIMH (Box 37, Folder 13.6)
- (Temporarily removed from shelf) (Box 38)
- HEW Site Visit to Notre Dame University 13.12 NDEA Counseling and Guidance Training Institute (Box 39, Folder 13.09)
- The White House - National Goals Research Staff 13.11 1970 White House Conference on Children and Youth (Oettinger) (Box 39, Folder 13.111)
- U.S. Office of Education ERIC Program (Box 39, Folder 13.10)
- National Evaluation Panel for Emotionally Disturbed Children (Moss) 13.20 National Advisory Child Health and Human Development Council - General Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 13.04)
- S-2 General Correspondence (Box 39)
- S-3 General Correspondence (Box 39)
- T-1 General Correspondence (Box 39)
- T-2 General Correspondence (Box 39)
- U General Correspondence
- V General Correspondence
- W-1 General Correspondence (Box 39)
- W-2 General Correspondence (Box 39)
- W-3 General Correspondence (Box 39)
- X General Correspondence
- Y General Correspondence
- Z General Correspondence
- 2 Past President - Felix Robb (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 Vice President for Academic Affairs - Hollis Moore (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 Dean of Administration - W.C. Jones (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 President Emeritus - Henry Hill (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 Dean of Admissions - W.C. Jones/Tracey Ramsey (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 Administrative Vice-President - George Conger (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 Dean of Undergraduate School - Phelps (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 Bursar-Mary McNultz (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 Dean of the Graduate School - Hunt (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2 Dean of Instruction - Norris (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-A College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-B College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-c College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-D College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-E College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-F College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-G College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-H College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-I College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-J College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-K College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-L College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-M College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-N College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-o College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-P College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-Q College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-R College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-S College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-T College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-U College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-V College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-w College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-X College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-Y College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- 2-Z College Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Vanderbilt University (Box 40, Folder 2.1)
- Administrative Cabinet (Box 40, Folder 3.0)
- General Information (Box 40, Folder 3.00)
- Faculty Conference (Box 40, Folder 3.001)
- Faculty Meeting (1957-1963) (Box 40, Folder 3.01A)
- E Mary Engel - Manuscripts and Correspondence (Box 41)
- D-1 General Correspondence: Da- Dn (Box 41)
- D:..2 General Correspondence: Do (Box 41)
- E-1 General Correspondence (Box 41)
- F General Correspondence
- G-1 General Correspondence: G - Go (Box 41)
- G-2 General Correspondence: Gr (Box 41)
- H-1 General Correspondence: H - Hill (Box 41)
- H-2 General Correspondence: Hilsinger (Box 41)
- I General Correspondence
- J General Correspondence
- K-1 General Correspondence: Ka-Ki (Box 41)
- K-2 General Correspondence: Kl (Box 41)
- L-1 General Correspondence: La - Lig (Box 41)
- L-2 General Correspondence: Lil (Box 41)
- M-2 General Correspondence: Me (Box 41)
- M-1 General Correspondence: M - May (Box 41)
- M-3 General Correspondence: Me (Box 41)
- N General Correspondence (Box 41)
- Kennedy Foundation Proposal (Box 43, Folder 3.63)
- Peabody Research and Developmental Center (Drummond) (Box 43, Folder 3.64)
- Child Study Center Advisory Committee (1964-1965) (Box 43, Folder 3.65)
- Southern Center for Improvement of Educational Opportunities (Drummond) (Box 43, Folder 3.66)
- Invention and Supportive Research With Young Deprived Children USOE Proposal (Susan Gray) (Box 43, Folder 3.67)
- Placement Office (Box 43, Folder 3.69)
- 1969-1970 Colloquium (Box 43, Folder 3.70)
- Round Table III (Box 43, Folder 3.71)
- General Correspondence Artwork Division (Box 43, Folder 4.0)
- College Budgets (Box 43, Folder 4.01)
- Resume of Grant Activities, 1966-1977 (charts, grants, overhead, etc.) (Box 43, Folder 4.011)
- Prelim Material (Box 43, Folder 4.02)
- Curriculum Committee (Box 43, Folder 4.03)
- Rosters (Box 43, Folder 4.04)
- Buildings, plans, changes, construction proposal, etc. (Box 43, Folder 4.05)
- Peabody Peabody (Box 43, Folder 4.07)
- Rhodes Proposal (Box 43, Folder 4.08)
- Staff Meetings (Box 43, Folder 4.09)
- Haywood's File of Letters from Psychology Doctoral Graduates (Box 43, Folder 4.10)
- Abstracts of Peabody Studies in Mental Retardation (Box 43, Folder 4.11)
- General Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 4.12A)
- NICHD: Reports, mimeographed materials, etc. (Box 43, Folder 13.201B)
- NICHD: Reports, mimeographed materials, etc. (Box 43, Folder 13.201C)
- NICHD: Reports, mimeographed materials, etc. (Box 43, Folder 13.201D)
- NICHD: Reports, mimeographed materials, etc. (Box 43, Folder 13.201E)
- NICHD: Orientation Program (Box 44, Folder 13.202)
- NICHD: Organization Handbook (Box 44, Folder 13.203)
- NICHD: Travel Vouchers and Statements of Earnings (Box 44, Folder 13.204)
- NICHD: Confidential Minutes of Advisory Council (Box 44, Folder 13.205)
- NICHD: Perinatal Study (Box 44, Folder 13.206)
- NICHD: Site Visits - Georgetown University (Box 44, Folder 13.207)
- NICHD: Site Visits - Washington State University (Box 44, Folder 13.207)
- NICHD: Site Visits - University of Colorado Medical Center (Box 44, Folder 13.207)
- NICHD: Site Visits - Western Carolina College (Cullowhee, N.C.) (Box 44, Folder 13.207A)
- NICHD: Site Visits - Western Carolina College (Cullowhee, N.C.) (Box 44, Folder 13.207B)
- NICHD: Booklets, rosters, general information, etc. (Box 44, Folder 13.208A)
- NICHD: Booklets, rosters, general information, etc. (Box 44, Folder 13.208B)
- NICHD: Booklets, legislation (Box 44, Folder 13.209)
- NICHD: Booklets, mental retardation information (Box 44, Folder 13.2010)
- Albert Einstein Hospital Material (Box 45, Folder 13.2011)
- NICHD: Planning Committee (Box 45, Folder 13.2012)
- NICHD: Conference on Learning (Box 45, Folder 13.2013A)
- NICHD: Conference on Learning (Box 45, Folder 13.2013B)
- NICHD and the Behavorial and Social Sciences (Box 45, Folder 13.2014)
- NICHD: Hearings on Labor, Health, Education and Welfare Appropriations (Box 45, Folder 13.2015)
- NIH General (Box 45, Folder 13.3)
- NIH Application Forms (Box 45, Folder 3.31)
- Research Career Awards Minutes of General Faculty Meetings of Peabody College (unfoldered) (Box 45, Folder 13.32)
- Faculty Advisory Council 3.01IB Faculty Advisory Council 3.012 Peabody Faculty Research Committee (Box 45, Folder 3.011A)
- Faculty Research Ethics Committee (Box 45, Folder 3.14)
- Faculty Handbook (Box 45, Folder 3.15)
- Letters of Recommendation: For Positions for Work (A-H) "XJtvmrsa wsbhubbbt. -Hmnvmmvivaiwsi? *"(B«»r.<ii«c (Box 45, Folder 3.02)
- Letters of Recommendation: For Positions for Work (I-Z) (Box 45, Folder 3.02)
- Letters of Recommendation: For Students to Schools, Scholarships (Box 45, Folder 3.2)
- Bureau of Appointments (Box 45, Folder 3.3)
- Peabody Development Council (Box 45, Folder 3.4)
- News Notes (Office of President) (Box 45, Folder 3.5)
- Presidential Selection Committee (Box 45, Folder 3.6)
- Library Materials - Correspondence (Box 45, Folder 3.11)
- Peabody Library School (Box 45, Folder 3.12)
- Library Materials Ordered (Box 45, Folder 3.13)
- Joint University Library (JUL): A Plan (1965-1975) (Box 45, Folder 3.1)
- Mental Retardation Institute (Box 45, Folder 3.2)
- GIRD - Group for Intellectual Research and Development (Box 45, Folder 3.3)
- American Council on Education (Box 47, Folder 8.11C)
- American Council on Education (Box 47, Folder 8.11B)
- American Psychiatric Association (Walter E. Barton) (Box 47, Folder 8.13)
- American Council on Education (Box 47, Folder 8.11A)
- HELP Newsletter (Parents Organization for Emotionally Disturbed Children) (Box 47, Folder 8.6)
- AAAS (American Association for the Advancement of Science) (Box 47, Folder 8.7)
- Council of the Southern Mountains (Box 47, Folder 8.9)
- American Association for Gifted Children (Box 47, Folder 8.10)
- Directory - State Association for Gifted Children (Box 47, Folder 8.31)
- Tennessee Mental Health Association (Box 47, Folder 8.4)
- Project Head Start (Box 47, Folder 8.5)
- SEPA (Southeastern Psychological Association) (Box 47, Folder 8.1)
- SSPP (Southern Society for Philosophy and Psychology) (Box 47, Folder 8.2)
- TPA (Tennessee Psychological Association) (Box 47, Folder 8.3)
- History of Psychology (Beginning Work on Bibliography) (Box 48, Folder 18.06)
- Doctoral Committee (Box 48, Folder 3.511)
- Doctoral Dissertation, Hold File (Box 48, Folder 3.512)
- Doctoral Dissertation, Hold File (Joseph J. Orze) (Box 48, Folder 3.5121)
- Doctoral Dissertation, Hold File (Juanita Prater) (Box 48, Folder 3.5122)
- Doctoral Dissertation, Hold File (Charles Weaver) (Box 48, Folder 3.5123)
- Doctoral Dissertation, Hold File (E.C. Sidney Reid) (Box 48, Folder 3.5126)
- Doctoral Dissertation, Hold File (Kathryn Wolff Nelson) (Box 48, Folder 3.5127)
- Material Ref; Composition of Doctoral Program (Box 48, Folder 3.513)
- Special Committee on Doctorate (Box 48, Folder 3.514)
- Committee on Subdoctoral Program (Box 48, Folder 3.515)
- Doctoral Scholarship Program (Box 48, Folder 3.516)
- Vanderbilt-Peabody Cooperative Study 4.06 Ethics (Box 48, Folder 3.52)
- Conference on Social Competence and Clinical Practice (Box 48, Folder 8.60)
- Spartanburg County Mental Health Association (1-28-65) (Box 48, Folder 8.62)
- Hillsborough County Mental Health Association (Tampa, Florida; 5-10-65) (Box 48, Folder 8.63)
- Hogg Foundation (Box 48, Folder 8.64A)
- Hogg Foundation (Box 48, Folder 8.64B)
- Hogg Foundation (books, reports) (Box 48, Folder 8.641B)
- Cosmos Club (Box 48, Folder 8.65)
- Tennessee Association of Counselor Educators and Supervisors (TACES) (Box 48, Folder 8.66)
- Nashville Committee on Foreign Relations (Box 48, Folder 8.67)
- Tennessee Association for Retarded Children and Adults, Inc. (TARCA) (Box 48, Folder 8.69)
- Davidson County Association for Retarded Children (Box 48, Folder 8.70)
- State of Tennessee Higher Education Facilities Commission (Box 48, Folder 8.71)
- Danforth Graduate Fellowships for Women (1969-1970) (Box 48, Folder 8.72)
- Urban League (Box 48, Folder 8.73)
- Tennessee Mid-South Regional Medical Plan (Box 48, Folder 8.74)
- "NAIL" Program (Box 48, Folder 8.75)
- College Entrance Examination Board (Box 48, Folder 8.76)
- Who's Who in American College and University Administration (Box 48, Folder 8.77)
- Great Decisions Program (Box 48, Folder 8.78)
- Appalachian Trailway News (Box 48, Folder 8.79)
- ETS (Educational Testing Service) (Box 48, Folder 8.81)
- Multi-Country Comprehensive Mental Health Center (Box 48, Folder 8.82)
- International Association of Workers for Maladjusted Children (Branch of the United States of America) (Box 48, Folder 8.83)
- (Black notebook) History of Psychology - Student Papers (Box 49)
- (Beige notebook) Miscellaneous (Black notebook) (Box 49)
- Dissertation by Nicholas Hobbs entitled Psychological Research and Servives in an Army Forces Convalescent Hospital, Ohio State University, 1946 (carbon copy) (Box 49)
- 5 Psychology 369: Advanced Seminar in Developmental Psychology (Spring Semester, 1968-1969) (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 369: History of Psychology (exams, answer sheets, keys, etc.,) Psychology 526: "The Historical Roots of Phenomenology and Existential Psychology, Introduction," by Walter E. Collins "A History of the Concept of Self-Actualization," by David Martin (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 526: History of Psychology (copies of old exams and keys, stored previously in #102 Psychology) Psychology 526: History of Psychology - Bibliography Psychology 526: Course Outline and General References (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 526: Book orders, films, reserve books requests, etc. (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 526: History of Psychology - Reading Assignment Sheets (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 544: Readings and Research (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Student Papers, Class of 1964-1965 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Student Papers, Psychology 556: Contemporary Psychology (book orders, reserves, and films for class) (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 556: Contemporary Psychology - Reading Schedule (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 526: History of Psychology - Steps in Preparing Bibliography (Box 49, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 556: Grade sheets, Registrar (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 556: Extra copies of guides of films (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 556: Contemporary Psychology - Plan for Course (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 556: Contemporary Psychology - Make-up Quizzes (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 556: Copies of old exams and keys (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 556: Contemporary Psychology (tests, keys, and evaluations) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 556: Contemporary Psychology (extra copies of past tests) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 593: Hobbs' notes, counseling, interviews, etc. (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 593: Personal Counseling (copies of old exams and keys stored previously in #102 Psychology) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 593: Hobbs' notes, counseling, interviews, etc. (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 593: Principles of Counseling - A Selected Bibliography (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 593: Principles of Personal Counseling - quarterly requests for books (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 593 I: Personal Counseling (NDEA Guidance Institute, Summer, 1963) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 613 (Spring, 1960) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 613 Therapy Reports
- 5 How People Feel About School Work (questionnaire) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Word Recognition Test
- 5 Education 55A: Human Development and Guidance (past tests) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 5 Psychology 700: Supervised Research (grade sheets, etc.) (Box 50, Folder 5)
- 8.1ID American Council on Education (Box 51, Folder 8)
- American Council on Education 8.1 IF American Council on Education (Box 51, Folder 8.11E)
- University Club of Nashville (Box 51, Folder 8.14)
- Congress of the International Association for the Scientific Study of Mental Deficiency (Box 51, Folder 8.15)
- National Advisory Committee for the National Society for Autistic Children (Box 51, Folder 8.16)
- National Society for Autistic Children, Incorporated (Box 51, Folder 8.161)
- Sigma Xi (Box 51, Folder 8.17)
- The Cleveland Conference (Box 51, Folder 8.23)
- U.M.O.S.E.A. and Other Foreign Publications, re: Child Welfare (Box 51, Folder 8.24)
- Castle Hill Symposium (Box 51, Folder 8.25)
- National Association for Mental Health (Box 51, Folder 8.27)
- (NARC) National Association for Retarded Children: Correspondence (Box 51, Folder 8.28)
- NARC Reports, booklets, etc. (Box 51, Folder 8.28A)
- NARC Reports, booklets, etc. (Box 51, Folder 8.28B)
- SREB General Correspondence: Southern Regional Education Board (Box 51, Folder 8.29)
- SREB Center for Emotionally Disturbed Children (Box 51, Folder 8.291)
- SREB Papers, Reports (1955-1956) (Box 52, Folder 8.291A)
- SREB Papers, Reports (1955-1956) (Box 52, Folder 8.291B)
- SREB Papers, Reports (1955-1956) (Box 52, Folder 8.291C)
- SREB Papers, Reports (1955-1956) (Box 52, Folder 8.291D)
- Social Science Research Council (Box 52, Folder 8.3)
- National Science Foundation (Box 52, Folder 8.31)
- Harvard Club of Nashville and Middle Tennessee (Box 52, Folder 8.32)
- (AAMD) American Association on Mentally Deficiency (Box 52, Folder 8.33)
- Residential Training Center for Mentally Retarded (Indiana University) (Box 52, Folder 8.331)
- Council for Exceptional Children (Box 52, Folder 8.39)
- Behavioral Science Newsletter (Box 52, Folder 8.40)
- Behavioral Science Frontiers in Education (Box 52, Folder 8.41)
- Regulations on Travel Under USPH Grants (Box 52, Folder 8.42)
- American Association of University Professors (Peabody Chapter) (Box 52, Folder 8.43)
- Vocational Rehabilitation Agency Project (Box 52, Folder 8.44)
- Testimony Before the Senate Committee on Public and Mental Health, Tennessee (1-28-59) (Box 52, Folder 8.45)
- Fairfax Academy (Box 52, Folder 8.46)
- Survey Research Center - University of Michigan (Box 52, Folder 8.47)
- President's Address to Congress on Mental Illness and Mental Retardation (Box 52, Folder 8.48)
- Experiment in International Living (Box 52, Folder 8.49)
- The Children's Foundation (Box 52, Folder 8.50)
- Florida Conference on Social Work (Box 52, Folder 8.52)
- Steering Committee - Congress on Mental Illness and Health (TMA) (Box 52, Folder 8.53)
- Oklahoma State Psychological Association Meeting (Box 52, Folder 8.54)
- American Orthopsychiatric Association (Box 52, Folder 8.55)
- North Carolina Advancement School (Box 52, Folder 8.56A)
- North Carolina Advancement School (Box 52, Folder 8.56B)
- Senior Citizens Program (Box 52, Folder 8.57)
- Job Corps (Johnson's Poverty Program) (Box 52, Folder 8.58)
- Project Re-ED, 1966 Conference of the Surgeon General (1-7-66) (Box 53, Folder 14.419)
- Project Re-ED, Kentucky Psychological Association (1-21-66) (Box 53, Folder 14.4120)
- The House of the Educated Man, An Architectural Conceit; Peabody Honors Program (May, 1966) (Box 53, Folder 14.4121)
- Helping Disturbed Children: Psychological and Ecological (Box 53, Folder 14.4122)
- A Sketch of a Plan to Improve the Quality of Life of Young Children in the United States (October, 1966) (Box 53, Folder 14.4123)
- Bettelheim, Bruno. The Empty Fortress: Infantile Autism and the Birth of the Self (Review) (Box 53, Folder 14.4124)
- The Responsible Child in a Responsible World, Williamsburg (July, 1967) (Box 53, Folder 14.4125)
- Re-Education, Reality, and Community Responsibility, APA (September, 1967) (Box 53, Folder 14.4126)
- Presentation to the National Advisory Committee, Second Annual Meeting, John F. Kennedy Center (April 2, 1967) (Box 53, Folder 14.4127)
- Statement by Nicholas Hobbs, "The Quality of Life of a People" (8-26-67) (Box 53, Folder 14.4128)
- Comments on Papers by Ekstein and Lovaas, Current Treatment Approaches to Psychotic Children, APA (September 1, 1967) (Box 53, Folder 14.4129)
- Introduction of Gardner Llndzey on Occasion of His Presidential Address, APA (9-3-67) (Box 53, Folder 14.4130)
- Henley, Arthur. Demon in M^ View (Book Review, 10-17-67) (Box 53, Folder 14.4132)
- "The Kennedy Center, the College, and the Community," Leadership Club, Peabody College (11-29-67) (Box 53, Folder 14.4134)
- "The Kennedy Center," Peabody Board of Trustees (4-15-68) (Box 53, Folder 14.4135)
- Presentation to National Advisory Committee, John F. Kennedy Center, Third Annual Meeting (4-1-68) (Box 53, Folder 14.4136)